混乱之子 前情提要
Previously on Sons of Anarchy...
你想把我们交给公众审判吗？
You trying this in the court of public opinion, Counselor?
我可不能控制媒体的观点和看法
I have no control of what the press gets ahold of or how they spin it.
是啊
Right.
为了摆脱牢狱之灾
Giving up the Sons of Anarchy is going to be
有人很愿意把混乱之子帮会供出来
a very popular get-out-of-jail-free card.
你和Lowen在搞什么鬼？
What are you doing with Lowen?
你要和Jax离婚？
You divorcing Jax?
你打算在监护人的事情上造反吗？
You planning on some kind of custody coup?
我对家人干嘛不关你的事
What I do with my family is none of your business.
婊子
Bitch!
老天
Jesus!
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
我的宝贝
My baby!
看你干的好事
Look what you did.
哦 不是我干的
Oh, I didn't do that.
不 就是你干的
Yes, you did.
我们都亲眼所见
We all saw it.
把她带走
Take her out of here.
你打算拿Gemma怎么办？
What are you gonna do about Gemma?
禁止令会让她离你和孩子们远远的
Restraining order keeps her away from you and the boys.
把事情搞得一团糟 让我心伤透了
It breaks my heart that you had to become something
你却认为这样做是对的
so wrong to do what you thought was right.
我这样做 是为了保护我的孩子 Wayne
I did it to protect my kids, Wayne.
我再也不会帮你了
I can't help you no more.
需要点什么吗 朋友
Need anything, friend?
是的 也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
我想你会喜欢这个
I think you'll like this one.
47页的内容非常精彩
It gets real good around page 47.
发生什么事？
What's going on?
Patterson 早上把我弄到她的办公室
Patterson pulled me into her office this morning.
是关于那个头条新闻的事？
About the headline?
她要把我毁了 小伙子 她威胁说
She's crushing me, kid;she's threatening to
要把港口归到郡长的管理下 这可是挡了大家的财路
bring in the sheriffs to police the port,
and that steps on everybody's game.
我打算交待那把枪的来源
I'm ready to give up the source of the KG-9.
那把枪不是Teller提供的
It wasn't Teller who supplied the gun.
是我
It was me.
我对那些死去的孩子负责
I'm responsible for the death of those children.
要是你还在乎那些孩子 你就应该交待清楚...所有的真相
If you cared about these kids, you'd
tell me everything... the whole truth.
我不清楚你打什么主意
I don't know where you're going with this, but I
但是 我的律师不在场 我不会吐一个字
ain't saying another word to you without my lawyer.
你不需要律师了
You don't need a lawyer.
是Toric杀害了Erin Byrne
Toric killed Erin Byrne.
他可以走了
He's free to go.
你是否后悔过....你回来？
Do you ever regret it... coming back?
很多事情 我可能有不同的选择
A lot of things I'd do differently.
我只是感觉到 我与你的距离如此遥远
I just feel so far away from you now.
让我回到你的心里
Please let me back in.
早安
Good morning.
你回来我好开心
I'm so glad you're home.
我也是
Me, too.
我去给你弄点咖啡
I'll make you some coffee.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦
Oh.
希望我们今天别再上头条新闻
Hopefully we didn't make the front page today.
没有
Nope.
似乎确实没有
Doesn't look like it.
我才起来没多久
Guess my 15 minutes are up.
我也有条大新闻给你听听
I got my own headline you need to hear.
昨天没告诉你 是不想破坏你刚回来的气氛
Didn't want to tell you last night, step on the homecoming.
大新闻？
Front-page-type stuff?
发生了什么事？
What's going on?
关于我和Tara的事
It's me and Tara.
糟糕透了
Shit happened.
真的想把这一切都告诉我吗？
Are you sure you want to tell me all this?
嗯 是的
Yeah, I do.
Clay没有在监狱里被干掉的原因 是因为我们需要他
The reason Clay wasn't killed inside is because we need him.
爱尔兰方面指定他接手在加州的枪支生意
The Irish want him to be point for guns here in Cali.
他们打算下周 在他转送途中劫囚车 救他出来
They're gonna take down his transport next week, bust him out.
老天
Jesus Christ.
哇哦
Wow.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
听上去太他妈疯狂了 老妈
That's some crazy-ass shit, Mama.
你有什么证据吗？
Can you prove any of it?
Wendy参与了Tara的勾当
Wendy was in on it with Tara.
她现在很内疚
Guilt got to her.
我认为她还是会站在我这边的
I think she'll back me up.
你是说 一个做父亲的 对于他所爱的人
You're talking about a father trying to wrap his brain
也就是孩子他妈 做出的令人发指的背叛行为
around some seriously heinous
而置之不理 宁愿把头埋在沙里
betrayal by the woman he loves, mother of his son.
我认为你需要的证据 不仅仅是一个瘾君子的话
I think you might need more than the word of a junkie.
特别是 这个瘾君子是他所厌恶的人
Especially a junkie he hates.
我想你没必要再告诉我其他什么
I don't think you should tell me anything else.
我知道 你在做着你想做的事
I know you're doing what you got to do.
让我们彼此的距离疏远
Putting distance between us.
我明白
I get it.
昨晚我冥思苦想了一夜 想怎样帮你洗脱那个指控 Tara
I spent all night trying to figure out how
to help you with these charges, Tara.
你做不到的
You can't.
是啊
Yeah.
但是我会保证 作为一个丈夫的承诺
But I can keep my promise as a husband.
坦诚相待
To be honest.
这一点以前我没做到
Which I haven't.
我一直想保护你 不管任何事情 显然我没有做到
I've been trying to protect you from
everything, which clearly hasn't worked.
完全没做到
At all.
现在 我明白了你的苦心 老妈
Now, I know you're trying, Mama.
你身上的麻烦 不应该成为你的负担
The struggle that I'm having with this
shit, that-that ain't your burden.
那得感激你没有对我不信任
Thanks for not doubting me.
或者至少你没表现出来
Or for at least not showing me that you do.
你心里埋藏着很多秘密 Gem
You got some heavy secrets, Gem.
我能看出来
I see them.
我也知道那些秘密的给你的负担
I see the weight of them.
它们带走了你的欢乐
How they drain the joy from you.
但是对于孩子们 你从来没有为此编造真相
But your babies... I know that you'd
never spin the truth about that.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
Me, too.
记得吗 自从你离开Stockton监狱以后 你就没说过“我爱你”
You know, since you got out of Stockton,
you haven't been able to say "I love you."
我知道 那段经历对你来说很痛苦
I know that must be hard for you.
对不起 我忍不住要告诉你
I'm sorry, I'll stop telling you.
告诉你我的感觉
Just know it's what I feel.
孤独的骑行在这尘世
Riding through this world  all alone
上帝将灵魂带走
God takes your soul
徒剩躯壳
You're on your own
像乌鸦掠过天际
The crow flies straight
直飞远方
A perfect line
缠绵在恶魔之床
On the devil's path
直至死亡
Until you die
才将这一世轨迹
Gotta look this life
看个端详
In the eye.
混乱之子 第六季 第九集
英语字幕：n17t01   翻译：Wilsonyy  校对：Dena
早上好
Good morning.
我要给你通报一下最新情况 警长
I need to update you, Lieutenant.
好的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
这边请
Here we are.
我听说昨晚Padilla昨晚被释放了
I understand that Padilla was released last night.
是的
That's right.
她的头发怎么了？
What happened to her hair?
那才是她真正的风格
Sister be doing it with the real flow.
不明白是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
我听说了被害者父亲的遭遇
I heard about what happened to the victim's father.
在Stockton自杀了
Suicide in Stockton.
不是从报纸上得知的
Not from the papers.
我和住在迪威逊大街的亚历山大聊过
I-I spoke to Alexander at Division Street.
哦
Oh.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
嗯 非常令人伤感
Yeah, it's very sad.
我想我还有部分心存感激
I guess a part of me is grateful...
在我乏味的工作中还有让我意外的事情
that something can still surprise me in this job.
让我没有完全变成铁石心肠
Makes me not completely made of stone.
暂时还没有
Yet.
我给你调派三个额外的队伍
I'm giving you three extra units.
我要你全天24小时 时刻监视Jax Teller
I want 24/7 surveillance on Jax Teller.
你认为这样动用我们的资源是最好的方式吗？
You think that's really the best use of our resources?
夫人 我很了解这帮家伙
Ma'am, I know these guys.
自从那个头条新闻出来后 他们完全变得像童子军一样守规矩
After those headlines,they'll go total Boy Scout.
不敢越雷池一步
Won't risk any business.
这是考验耐性和持久性的时候
It's about consistency and patience.
现在我们把气氛缓和下来 转过身去 眼光放到别处
The minute we ease up, turn our backs, look the other way,
这段时间我们就放任其他惨剧的发生
that's the minute we allow another tragedy to happen.
对付这帮家伙来硬的 我没问题 你呢 警长？
You don't have a problem stepping hard
on these guys, do you, Lieutenant?
不
No.
没问题
I don't.
很好
Good.
立即开始监视行动
Surveillance begins immediately.
很快你就会得到增援
You'll have backup within the hour.
弄得很干净啊 Chucky
Looking clean, Chucky.
过奖了
Thank you.
这就是为什么你是个怪胎
And that's why you're a freak.
嘿
Hey.
欢迎回来 兄弟
Welcome back, my brother.
嘿 哥们
Hey, buddy.
爱尔兰人的生意经念得怎样？
How'd the Irish sales pitch go?
还不错 兄弟
Good, man.
和我们大多数买家联络上了
Connected with most of our buyers.
他们还是希望和Clay打交道 但似乎愿意接受这种转变
They still want to talk to Clay,but they seemed open to change.
他们也理解了我们为什么要退出
They get why we're stepping away.
很好
Good.
和意大利人不好谈
Couldn't get a sit-down with the Italians.
我认为 私人交情变了 和他们就不好打交道
I don't think the personnel change is gonna land too well with them.
爱尔兰人有安排
Irish are setting it up.
他们找了监狱内部的人 他能给Clay弄部电话 让他联络
They got someone inside that's gonna get
a phone to Clay, have him reach out.
搞定所有买家
Lock down all the buyers.
好吧
All right.
他们与Clay联系上以后 你负责跟进
You follow up with everyone after they talk to Clay.
好的
Aye.
早上好
Morning.
不好意思 打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
哇哦
Wow.
你还没死？
You didn't die yet?
黄土每天都埋上来一点
A little every day.
见到你真高兴
Good to see you, Chief.
嗯 我也是 Bobby
Yeah, you, too, Bobby.
有什么需要吗 队长？
What do you need, Cap-a-tain?
给我几分钟时间 老大
Just a minute of your time there, Pres.
嗯 好的
Yeah, okay.
告退了 先生们
Excuse us, gentlemen.
一会楼上见
I'll see you upstairs.
嗯 好的
Yeah, all right.
给你来杯咖啡？
Can I get you some coffee?
你有 呃 啤酒吗？
You got any, uh, beer back there?
现在就到了泡吧时间？
Miller time already?
吃早餐还能要你命呢
Breakfast of terminally-ill champions.
过来坐吧
Sit down.
嘿 我想告诉你
Hey, I wanted you to know.
Tara说 有你陪着她和孩子们真是太好了
Tara told me how good you've been with her and the boys.
近来太多的麻烦事 一直没机会说声“谢谢”
With all the shit going on,haven't had a chance to say
真的很感谢你的照顾 朋友
thank you, but appreciate you looking out, man.
嗯
Yeah.
这是 呃  应该的
It's, uh, no problem.
你真的有个不错的家庭 孩子
You got a real nice family there, son.
是啊 有些确实不错
Yeah, some of them.
是啊
Right.
我明白这也许不关我事 但是...
I know it probably ain't none of my business, but...
我比任何人都了解你老妈
I know your mom longer than anybody.
小的时候我们经常吃霸王餐
We used to dine and dash this place when we were kids.
是啊 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我知道你很关心她 Wayne
Look, I know you care about my mom, Wayne.
可不仅仅是这样 孩子....
It's not just that, son...
老天
Jesus Christ.
搞什么？
What the hell?
喂 你到底在干什么？
Hey! What the hell you doing?!
喔.....喔
Whoa... whoa!
哦 搞什么？
Oh! What the hell?!
该死的
Holy shit!
放开我
Let go of me!
你是谁？
Who are you?
喂 你为什么要这么干？
Hey! Why'd you do that?
强奸啦
Rape!
开玩笑吧
Seriously?
放开我
Let go of me!
来人呐...拿开...
Somebody... take...!
好吧 好吧
All right! All right!
发生什么事情？
What's that all about?
带上你们的枪和吵死人的摩托滚蛋吧
You need to take your guns and
your loud bikes and just go.
你们这帮人都滚出这里
You all need to get out of here.
欢迎
Welcome.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢光临
Thanks for coming.
欢迎
Welcome.
进来吧
Come on in.
你好吗？
How you doing?
欢迎 欢迎
Welcome. Welcome.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
很好 进来吧
Good. Come on in.
很好
Good.
多谢各位的光临 先生们
I'd like to thank you all,
gentlemen, for coming today.
你们做了一个正确的选择
You made the right choice.
今天读书的内容是约翰福音第八章第三十二节 真理的力量
Today's reading is from John 8:32 on power of truth.
请大家打开圣经
Will you all now please open your Bibles.
那是Gary Putner家的孩子
It was Gary Putner's kid.
她从12岁就进出少年管教所
She's been in and out of juvie and rehab since she was 12.
是个问题少年
Got a few problems.
是啊 她用水管扳手来反击吧
Yeah. She's working them out with a pipe wrench.
为什么是我的车倒霉？
Why my bike?
我是说真的
I mean, really?
所有的小姑娘都和我有仇吗？
Do all teenage girls just hate me?
是的
Yes.
是
Yep.
哦 是吧
Oh. Yeah.
我们认识那个Putner吗？
We know this Putner guy?
Clay可能认识
Clay might have.
为Oswald干活之前 他是个熟练的技师
He was a journeyman mechanic
before he went to work for Oswald.
现在他是厂里设备部的领班
He's an equipment foreman at the mill.
嗯 但是我们和他没什么过节 不怎么记得他
Yeah, but we never had a beef with
the guy... not that I can remember.
没有孩子他妈？
No mother?
她去世了
She was killed.
车祸
Car accident.
18号公路上 就在孩子出生后不久
Highway 18, just after the kid was born.
可能这就是原因
That might be the connection.
那个拖车把你老爸撞了以后 产生连环撞车
It was the pile-up caused by the tractor-trailer,
也就殃及到了她
jackknifed after it hit your dad.
这就是说 因为她妈妈的死责怪到我们头上
So she blames us for her mother's death.
18年以后的报复？
18 years later?
难说
I don't know.
人们往往对悲痛有不同的表达方式
People grieve in strange ways.
哦 糟了
Ah, shit.
他们是为了那个女孩的事情来的吗？
Think they're here 'cause of the girl?
要我去搞清楚吗？
Want me to go find out?
不用 我来
No, I got it.
早上好
Morning.
嗯
Yeah.
这儿怎么了？
What happened there?
不清楚
I don't know.
很明显有人对这里卖的冰激凌不满意
Clearly someone doesn't like ice cream.
对甜品严重过敏的人 是吧？
Extremely lactose intolerant, huh?
很对
That's right.
我猜你不是为了我们这破了一块玻璃而来吧
Guessing you're not here about my broken window.
不 不是
No, I'm not.
这段时间 你们得置于我们的监视下
You're gonna have a shadow for a little while.
这不是我说了算
It's not my call.
是Patterson？
Patterson?
她在寻找枪支来源 并且她的疑犯名单上只有一个名字
She's looking for the gun source, and
she only has one suspect on her list.
好吧
Okay.
跟踪你们的尾巴肯定会有的
This tail is gonna happen.
不要让我们难做 好吗？
Let's not make it ugly, all right?
好吧 我理解
No, I get it.
很好
All right.
走了 哥们
Fellas.
妈的
Shit.
我们新长出来的小尾巴
Our new tail.
这可不妙
This is bad, Jackie.
下周我们会很忙很忙
We got a very, very busy week ahead of us.
我知道
I know.
找机会我们把那个话题聊完
We need to finish that conversation.
下次吧
We will.
好的
All right.
Barosky找你
It's Barosky.
说有急事
Says it's urgent.
呃 让他来找我们
Well, he's gonna have to come to us.
到Diosa碰头
Diosa.
你听见他说了？
You heard him?
到Diosa
Diosa.
好了 随时给我通报Clay的情况
All right, keep me updated on Clay.
你和Juice 把那姑娘找出来
You and Juice, find the girl.
好
Yeah.
我去见见Charlie
And let's go see Dirty Charlie.
Hap 跟我一起去
Hap, come with us.
薪水收入已经转到一个新的账户
Salaried income has been shifted into a new account.
很好
Good.
现金怎么办？
What about the cash?
保险箱有你们两个人的名字
Safety deposit box is in both your names.
现金是他的
Cash is his.
我这只是离开 不是把他扫地出门
It's about getting away,not cleaning him out.
这个是证人名单
Here's a list of character witnesses.
还能想到其他人吗？
Anyone else you can think of?
名单人不多啊
That's a short list.
行了 挺好的
No, it's fine.
我仔细查看过你的病历
I looked over your medical documentation...
怀孕证明 超声波检查报告 医生的签名...
positive pregnancy, ultrasounds, doctor's signatures...
都被关照过....都经Margaret Murphy之手
all expedited... by Margaret Murphy.
利用伪造的病历获得监护权可是重罪
Using false medical records to
substantiate a custody hold is a felony.
我明白
I know that.
离开庭还有两周时间
We're two weeks away from standing in front of a jury.
如果你还有什么剧本要演 我现在必须清楚
If there's any more drama you've
got planned, I need to know now.
所有你都知道
You know everything.
于是耶稣对那些信奉他的犹太人说
So Jesus said to the Jews who believed Him,
“如果你们遵从我的教导 你们才是我真正的门徒”
"If you abide in my Word,you are truly my disciples."
“你们将掌握真理，只有这个真理让你们得以自由”
"You will know the truth and this truth will set you free."
瞧 约翰
See, John...
他不是谈及你的或我的真理 他谈及的是上帝的真理
he ain't talking about your truth or my
truth, he's talking about God's truth.
阿门
Amen.
作为一个凡人 我们无法掌握真理
As mortal men, we can't know real truth.
这是为什么？
And why?
是因为我们是说谎者？
Is it because we are liars?
还是因为我们很邪恶或者不值得信任？
Is it because we are evil or untrustworthy?
不是的
No.
我们之所以是凡人 是因为我们生而有罪
We have the truth of man because
we were born with the sin of man!
这是原罪 兄弟们 就是这原罪让我们看不到上帝和他的真理
It is sin, my brothers, that keeps
us from knowing God and His truth!
有道理
That's right.
原罪
Sin!
我们每个人都带着模糊的眼镜
Those dirty glasses that we all wear.
正是这副眼镜 让我们每个人所说的 所做的 都是出于自身考虑
It is what makes everything we say,
everything we do, self-motivated!
这样怎能让我们认知到上帝和他的真理呢？
So how do we get to know God and His truth?
如何让我们看到 除了我们自私的欲望之外的东西呢？
How do we see beyond our own selfish desires?
如何让我们得以解脱呢？
How do we set ourselves free?
上帝啊
Jesus.
阿门 上帝啊
Amen, Jesus.
Amen, Jesus!
让我们澄清一些事情 大嘴巴
Let me get something straight, Rev.
某个犹太佬被钉在十字架上 就像 呃 我也说不清楚
Some Jew gets nailed to a
cross, like, uh, I don't know,
一千多年也没人在乎 现在他将变成救命屁
a thousand who-gives-a-shit years ago, and
he's gonna be the magic pill that pulls all
挽救我们这帮人渣 带给我们快乐和自由？
of us scumbags to happiness and freedom?
是的 会实现的 我的兄弟
Yes, it will, my brother.
哇哦
Wow.
Wow!
你知道上帝给了我什么 兄弟？
You know what God gave me, brother?
你知道是什么让我解脱？
You know what sets me free?
小妞
Pussy.
甜美 圣洁的小妞
Sweet, holy pussy.
你们知道吗 上帝 他把人类降生在这个星球上有三个原因：
You see, God, He put man on this planet for three reasons:
进食...挣斗....还有糟蹋小妞
eating... fighting... and tearing up tight, wet pussy!
够了 人犯
That's enough, inmate!
那..那就是我擦净黑色眼镜的方法 我的兄弟
That... that is what cleans my dark glasses, my brother.
给我闭嘴 坐下 Morrow
Shut up and sit down, Morrow.
我不能坐下
I can't sit!
我心中有上帝
I got the Lord in me!
他要我站着 他要我讲经 他要我布道
He wants me up, He wants me
preaching, He wants me to spread
用小妞来治病救人 用小妞来救赎 让我赞美小妞吧
pussy the healer, pussy the redeemer...
can I get a "Amen" for pussy!
走吧
Let's go.
你给我滚出去 混蛋
You're out of here, asshole!
我“嗅到”了真理的味道 兄弟
I "nose" the truth now, brother!
我解脱了
I'm free.
甜美的小妞让我解脱了
Sweet pussy has set me free!
嘿
Hey.
很高兴你回来 哥们
Glad you're back, brother.
谢谢 兄弟
Thanks, mano.
见到你很高兴
Good to see you.
我们知道那些都是扯淡的事
We knew it was all bullshit.
是啊 你懂的 正义终将获胜 对吧？
Yeah, you know, justice prevails, right?
Barosky来之前 我们得先聊聊
We need to catch up before Barosky comes over here, ruins our day.
一些家事
Family thing.
好的 当然
Yeah. Sure.
我希望谈的是你的家事
I'm hoping it's your family you need to talk about.
Gemma现在就是我的家人 兄弟
Gemma is my family now, mano.
嗯 那好啊 我正打算和她绝交
Well, that's good, 'cause I'm about done with her.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I'm seeing that.
听着 我...我知道这种感觉很糟
Look, I... I know how bad this feels.
但是我觉得 你应该回头想想 用另一种眼光看看发生了什么
But I think that you should go back,
take another look at what happened.
从中找到事实真相 Jax
Find the truth in all of this, Jax.
我已经知道了真相 Nero
I already know the truth, Nero!
不...不..
No... no...
怎么？ 你认为我老婆撒谎？
What? You think my wife is a liar?
喔
Whoa!
我只是说事情比你想象的要复杂 兄弟
I'm just saying it's a lot more complicated, bro, than you...
好了 我知道了
Look, I get it.
你爱我老妈 你愿意站在她一边 那是你的选择
You're in love with my mom, you're staying
in her corner, that's your choice.
但是 假如我们要继续一起做生意
But if we're going to keep doing business together,
我和我家人的事情你不能过问
the shit that went down between me and my family is off-limits.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
这种内容谈话不会再有第二次了
This conversation doesn't happen again.
不管和谁
With anyone.
Jax...
老大...Charlie和那位熟女来了
Boss... Charlie and the MILF madame are here.
好的
All right.
走吧 拍档
Let's go, partner.
见过我们的Boby了？
So you met Bobby?
是的
Yes.
很高兴你把狗头军师也带来了
Glad you brought the think tank.
我们或许用得上
We may need them.
你交保释金出来的？
You pull bail?
他们没什么证据
They had nothing.
只得放我走人
Had to let me go.
你倒是好了
Good for you.
你得了自由 我却得关门大吉
While you were getting freed up, I was getting shut down.
违反卫生条例 来自地方检察官的“恭贺”
Health violations, compliments of our district attorney.
我还以为 你可以利用受害人的父亲死了的事做点文章呢
I thought you were gonna use the victim's dad fubar as leverage.
这个狡猾的婊子从另外的方向偷袭我 让我有口难言
That pitch bitch is coming at us sideways, and I
can't prove she had anything to do with that.
我们的三陪生意的申请评估也没过关...被否了
We didn't make the escort rating, either... denied.
原因不明
Unspecified reasons.
不再会有Diosa了
No Diosa Del Sur.
该死的
Goddamn.
她想让你为校园枪击案担罪 兄弟
She wants you for that school shooting, man.
并且她会继续逼死每一个和你一路的人
And she's gonna continue to
strangle everybody in bed with you.
眼下 听好了 我既不会当告密者 也不是殉道者
Now, listen, kid, I ain't no rat
but I ain't no martyr, either.
我来想办法
I'll figure it out.
想什么办法 Jax？
How, Jax?
瞧 这个Pattern...她手里什么证据也没有 她要孤注一掷
Look, Patterson... she's desperate; she got nothing.
她只是狗急跳墙
She's gonna move off of all this shit.
我们只要稍安勿躁 等着瞧
We just got to wait it out.
不 你不在Stockton 你可以等
No, you got to wait.Out of Stockton.
不好意思 我可承担不起
I'm sorry, but I can't take the hit.
我得撤了
I got to eject.
和帅哥Jax和摩托骑士们道别吧
Say so long to Handsome Jack and the biker brigade.
别这样 Charlie
Come on, Charlie.
Nero说得对
Nero's right.
这正中Pattern的下怀...以莫须有的罪名搞我们
This is exactly what Patterson wants...
to hurt us 'cause she's got no case.
我知道 小伙子 我知道
I know, kid, I know.
但是眼下 这也是我的需求
But right now, it's what I want, too.
现在 我只有抱歉了
Now, look, I'm sorry.
事情有转机的话 通知我
Things change, you let me know.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我没料到他会在
Didn't know he was gonna be here.
老妈 也许我们该去里面的工作室....
Mama, maybe we should go into the studio...
别麻烦了
Don't bother.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
别打发他帮你做那些卑鄙的勾当
Just don't send him to do your dirty work.
没人打发我做什么
Nobody sent me to do anything.
我只是想帮忙而已
I was just trying to help.
别把火撒在别人身上
Don't take it out on him.
是啊 好吧 我想他现在知道更好
Yeah, well, I think he knows better now.
更糟糕的事情你却不知道
Too bad you don't.
你知道 他为了帮会做了什么吗？
You have any idea what he just did for you and the club?
Gem Gem...别 别 别
Gem, Gem... No, no, no.
他应该知道
He needs to know.
什么？
What?
地方检察官要他出卖你
D.A. wanted him to give you up.
他不肯
He wouldn't.
但是他知道那个婊子不会善罢甘休
But he also knew that that bitch would keep coming.
于是他承认自己是枪支的来源
So he gave himself up as the gun source.
这是真的？
Is that true?
嘿 你知道 这不碍事
Hey, you know, it-it didn't matter.
在我供出自己之前 我的律师发现
By the time I was gonna make
this deal, my lawyer found out
那个警长从Toric住的旅馆里发现证据
that the sheriffs, they had
pulled evidence from Toric's
证实了他才是杀害Erin的凶手
hotel room, proved that he was
the one that killed Erin.
于是 Patterson 他不得不放我走
So, Patterson, she had to let me go.
我不知道她把你逼成那个样子
I didn't realize she was bending you like that.
是啊  嗯....她 呃 绝不会善罢甘休的 老弟
Yeah, well... she, uh, ain't gonna
stop until she draws blood, man.
是啊
Yeah.
来吧 宝贝
Come on, babe.
你没事吧？
You all right?
不 不太好
No, not really.
Nero说的对
Nero's right.
Patterson不会善罢甘休
Patterson ain't gonna stop.
把所有弟兄都叫上
Call everyone.
来议事堂
Chapel.
我们得投票表决
We need to take a vote.
嘿 我们搞到了Putner家的地址 哥们
Hey. We got an address for Putner, man.
离这只隔了几条街
It's actually a few blocks from here.
那地方叫Willow Gulch
It's Willow Gulch.
很好 我们出发
All right, let's go.
好的
All right.
好的 走吧
All right, come on.
你是Putner
You Putner?
是的
Yeah.
我叫Jax Teller
Jax Teller.
我找你们家孩子
I'm looking for your kid.
我也在找她
Me, too.
我听说了怎么回事
Heard about what happened.
你就是那个要找她的人？
You the one who chased her?
是的
Yeah.
我没有伤害她
I didn't hurt her.
我只是要些答案
I just want some answers.
明白了
I get that.
进来吧
Come on in.
Brooke有些毛病
Brooke's got some stuff.
焦虑 易走极端
Anxiety, bipolar.
她妈妈也一样
Her mom had it, too.
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
知道
Yeah.
那就是她袭击我们的原因 你是这么认为的吗？
Is that why she attacked us, do you think?
就因为我老爸的原因？
Because of my dad?
这周我们过得很艰难
Been a rough week.
我失去房子
I lost the house.
我们得卷铺盖走人
We've been packing shit up.
刚好发现很多她老妈的相片
Came across a lot of photos of her mom.
还发现当时 关于她老妈的报纸新闻
Found the newspaper article about her death.
她马上认为是你老爸引起的连环撞车 导致她老妈的死亡
First time she realized your dad
caused the pileup that killed her mom.
我估计 以她胡思乱想的小脑瓜 她把仇算在你们头上了
I guess, in her messy little brain, she blames you guys.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不 我理解
No, I get it.
这上面就是你老婆
That your wife?
是的
Yeah.
Emily和我
Me and Emily.
怎么了？
Why?
她看上去很眼熟
She looks familiar.
我知道
I know.
我也会这样
Happens to me, too.
看别人的时候...好像也看到她
I see her a lot...in other people.
那么你知道孩子大概会在哪？
So you got any idea where your kid might be?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是她总要回来
She always comes home, though.
我会和她谈谈 把事情说清楚
I'll talk to her and straighten this out.
嗯 好吧
Yeah, okay.
我会赔偿你的损失
We'll pay for the damage.
不 不用担心这个
No, don't worry about that.
多谢
Thank you.
嘿
Hey.
来
Here you go.
吃下去
Hey, take that.
好了吗？
Ready?
真棒
Awesome.
谢谢
Thank you.
一会儿见
I'll see you later.
你找Jax？
You looking for Jax?
不 我是 呃 希望能和你谈谈
No. I was, uh, hoping I could talk to you.
没问题
Sure.
给他吃的药 呃 是治他的先天缺陷？
Is that for his,uh, birth defect?
是的 心率失常
Yeah. Heart arrhythmia.
这病似乎不能阻止他活泼好动
Doesn't seem to slow him down.
嗯 是的
No, it doesn't.
你感觉怎样？
How are you feeling?
还行
Fine.
我估计你来这 不是只为了解我家人的健康状况吧
I'm assuming you're not just here to
check on the health of my family.
实际上是的
Actually, I am.
情绪健康方面
Emotional health.
我们正设法对付
Well, we're all getting through it.
不是每个人都如此
Not everyone.
医生 你知道 我感觉你不是一个有恶意的人
Doc, you know, you don't strike me
as being a malicious kind of person.
我敢肯定 不管你和Gemma之间发生什么事情
I'm sure whatever it was that happened
between you and Gemma,
一定有你认为正当的理由
you did what you thought was right.
是Gemma袭击了我
Gemma attacked me.
导致了流产
Caused a miscarriage.
是啊 我请求你换个角度看待问题
Right. I guess I'm asking if you could
take another look at what's been done.
你们的家庭已经产生了裂痕
The rip it's causing in your family.
你不用理会我们的家事
You don't get to weigh in on my family.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
是 我不了解 但是你我都了解Gemma
No, I don't, but I do know Gemma and so do you.
她不会服软的
She's not gonna lay down for this.
也许我们都应该想个折中的办法
Maybe we could find some kind of middle ground here.
如果不能的话...对每个人来说都不得安宁
'Cause if not... this is not gonna end up well for anyone.
也包括你
Including you.
你知道和她在一起的男人的下场
You see what happens to the men she's with.
一个死了 另一个进了监狱
One husband dead, another in jail.
是啊 哎 你知道 这就是生活
Yeah, well, you know,that's the life.
不 是毒妇
No, it's the wife!
是她杀了John Teller
She killed John Teller!
也许不会用同样的方式对付Clay
Probably would've done the same to Clay.
你想善终吗？
You want it to end well?
我建议你退出来 免得到时你也死得难看
I suggest you get out now before you end up dead, too.
他就是那个在小教堂里发狂的那位？
Is he the one who flipped out in the chapel?
是的 医生
Yeah, Doc.
他现在平静下来了
He's calm now.
没有威胁了
He's secure.
好的 我知道了
Okay. I got it.
去六号房帮帮Nance
Go help Nance in six.
Tanner又在搞事了
Tanner had another episode.
糟糕 好的
Shit. Yeah, okay.
你是Morrow？
You Morrow?
是的
Yeah.
下一次换班之前 你有40分钟的时间
You got 40 minutes till the next rotation.
你要是被抓了 就算是出卖了我
You get caught, you give me up.
我会把你拖到这里绑上 注射3倍的镇静剂
I'll pull you in here, strap you down,
fry your brain with a
把你的脑子好好烤烤
triple dose of Thorazine.
这就是你当医生立下的誓言吗？
What part of the Hippocratic oath is that?
你的爱尔兰朋友付的钱 还不足够让我栽跟头
Same part that says your mick friends
don't pay enough for me to take a fall.
Murphy 夫人 Knowles医生给你的 十分钟前
Ms. Murphy, from Dr. Knowles,ten minutes ago.
谢谢
Thank you.
Tara?
她回家了
She went home.
我可以马上把保安叫来
I can have security here in an instant.
没必要
No need.
我在想你们怎么做到的
I debated how to do this.
我的行事方式.....你们这样对付我...
The way I feel... what you did to me...
我本来可以把你的细脖子扭断
I could squeeze the swallow out of that pale white throat.
但这只会让你觉得更有正义感
But that would just give you a greater sense of righteousness.
现在我来告诉你我会怎么做
So let me tell you what's gonna happen now.
我会把这些伪造Tara怀孕和流产的病历
I'm gonna take those medical records documenting Tara's
递交给医院的董事会
pregnancy and her miscarriage, and I'll
present them to the hospital board.
让他们知道 他们的新院长是个骗子
Let them know that their Neonatal
administrator is a bit of a grifter.
你和我的话 他们更愿意相信谁
It would be my word against yours.
这我倒想知道
That's all I needed to know.
多谢了 红鼻头
Thanks, Red.
你什么意思？
What does that mean?
意思是 如果怀孕这件事情确有其事
It means if the pregnancy was legit,
你不会告诉我 说这些病历是真的 还说我疯了
you would've told me that those
documents were real and called me crazy.
你没法证明
You can't prove anything.
哦 我不需要证明什么
Oh, I don't need to prove it.
我只需要比那个瘾君子更可靠的消息来源 去告诉我的儿子
I just needed a more reliable source
than a junkie to share with my son.
他将会去证实
He's gonna be the one to prove it.
当他这样做时 我现在告诉你 红鼻头...
And when he does, I'll tell you right now, Red...
这个州可没有足够的保安来保障你的安全
there won't be enough security in this state to keep you safe.
同意
Yea.
我代表West 和 Montez投票 他们也同意
Proxied West and Montez, they're a yea.
同意
Yea.
很好
All right.
我去出个价码
I'll go make the offer.
把他带进来
Send him in.
请坐
Have a seat.
我不得不说 我很惊讶 你和我面对面坐着
I must say, I'm rather surprised
to see you sitting across from me.
没人比我更惊讶
No more surprised than I am.
说说你来这贵干？
So why are you here?
混乱之子是由我父亲 John Teller一手创建
Sons of Anarchy was started by my father, John Teller.
他一直希望俱乐部合法化
He always wanted a legitimate club.
就为这个目标 他死了
Died pursuing that.
我没兴趣听你讲历史
I'm not in a mood for a history lesson.
为何你不开门见山 Teller先生
Why don't you get to it, Mr. Teller.
我来这就是和你谈价码
I'm here to make you an offer.
和我谈价...
To make me...
哇哦
Wow.
你可真有胆量 小伙子
You really have some balls, kid.
我还知道卖KG-9的爱尔兰人的情况
I also have an Irishman who sells KG-9s.
爱尔兰共和军？
IRA?
如假包换的爱尔兰共和军
Real IRA.
就是现在爱尔兰天主教革命之王
Current kings of the Irish Catholic revolution.
那么你的价码是什么？
So what are you offering?
Gaalan O'Shay
Gaalan O'Shay.
你可以去联邦调查局查查
You can check with the feds.
他可是条大鱼
He's a big win.
我可以把他交出来 附赠一船的枪支
I will deliver him with a shipment of guns.
干脆利落
Open and shut.
什么时候 什么方式 把这条“大鱼”交出来？
And when and how would you deliver this "big win"?
十天以后
It'll happen in the next ten days.
怎样做到 那是我的事情
The "how" is my job.
这是一个很大胆的提议啊
It's a very bold proposition.
何不告诉我 你想得到什么好处？
So why don't you tell me what's in it for you.
豁免混乱之子 一切关于贩卖枪支的指控
Immunity for the MC for all gun charges.
包括过去以及现在的
Past and present.
我希望有一个合法的俱乐部
I want a legitimate club.
但是如果大家都对我们恨之入骨 那可就成不了
That can't happen while people try to crush us,
那会毁了我们的生意
ruining all of our business relationships.
先在Stockton放我们一马
Let us breathe in Stockton.
我们不会干犯法的勾当 暴力活动也会停止
We won't break the law and the violence stops.
就这些？
That's it?
如果你真的认为你能交出爱尔兰共和军 那么我想
If you thought you could deliver
the IRA, then I figure you would
至少你会提出个人要求
at least also have a personal request.
确实
I do.
你必须重新审审Tara的案子
You need to look at Tara's case again.
Toric才是案子的关键所在
Toric was the one connecting the dots that didn't exist.
Tara确实不知道Otto会对付那个护士
Tara had no idea what Otto was gonna do to that nurse.
这点我们都清楚
We both know that.
据我所知 这样的巧合太难发生了
What I know and what I can prove rarely come together.
那么....对这些事情 我都应该善意的推测？
So... I'm supposed to expedite all of these things on good faith?
都把它们当成真的？
Just assume it's all real?
不需要什么善意
You don't need faith.
你只要睁一只眼闭一只眼放过去 给我们一些空间让我们动起来
Just have everything ready to go, and
give us the space to put it in motion.
假如爱尔兰人发现我们被跟踪 整件事情就吹了
If the Irish think we're being
tailed, this whole thing implodes.
到时我会告诉你到哪找到Gaalan和那些枪支
I'll tell you where to find Gaalan and the guns.
那么你和你们那帮人 就这样轻易逃脱 连毛皮都不用掉一根？
And you and your crew, you just skate away
without so much as a slap on the wrist?
他们会血腥反抗 你才能抓到我 女士
You can slap my wrists until they're bloody, lady.
我可不在乎
I don't give a shit.
我在给你大大的好处
I'm giving you a win well above your pay grade.
让你立下大功 还能全身而退
You get your devil and you punch
your ticket out of this cesspool.
那么就让我们别再纠结什么正义了
So let's not get too lost in righteousness.
我是个无法无天的混蛋 而你是正义的卫道士
I'm the scumbag outlaw, and
you're the pillar of justice.
都不喜欢看着镜子里的自己
And neither one of us likes looking
at ourselves in the mirror.
我们成交吗？
Do we have a deal?
10天之内 要是我听不到你的消息
If I don't hear from you within ten days...
我会花上 我还在位的七个月时间
I will spend the last seven months in this office
我会在法律的允许范围内 让你生不如死
making your life as miserable as the law allows.
还要算上你老婆...等到你儿子中学毕业 她才能从监狱出来
And your wife... she will be in jail until
your boys graduate from high school.
好吧
Okay.
我会查短信
We'll check messages.
好的
Fine.
大叔 你有钥匙吗？
Uncle T, you got the key?
嘿 好的
Hey. All right.
谢谢
Thanks.
有啊 在这
You got it. Right here.
你想买下来？
Want to buy it?
我们减价大拍卖
We're having a fire sale.
屁话
Shit.
你该庆幸没人受伤
You're lucky no one was hurt.
是啊
Yeah.
你有什么打算？
What're you gonna do?
等着保险公司计算损失
Waiting for the insurance to come up with a number.
很明显 我们可没有“炸损险”
Apparently we didn't have C-4 coverage.
有什么需要吗？
What do you need?
你的木材库房我们不再使用了
We're done with your lumber warehouse.
我们退出了贩枪生意
Moving out of guns.
亡羊补牢 为时不晚 我是这么认为的
Better late than never, I guess.
就这些
That it?
不
No.
有个在你厂里工作的家伙
There's a guy that works for you at the mill.
名叫Gary Putner
Gary Putner.
是的
Yeah.
很不错的伙计 他怎么了？
Good worker. What about him?
他失去了他的房子
He's losing his house.
他也没什么其他收入
He's got a single income.
还有个问题儿童
Kid with some problems.
如果你能帮他一把 我很感谢
I'd like it if you could help him.
我只是他的雇主 不是他的神仙姐姐
I'm his employer, not his fairy godmother.
别这样 Oswald 你有贷款机构又有高利贷公司
Come on, Oswald, you got a
credit union and a loan company.
别让他失去房子
Don't let the guy lose his home.
我想帮他 但是我们也难自保
I'd help him, but we're tapped.
这对你很重要吗？
Why's this so important to you?
我也说不好
I don't know.
嘿 算我欠你的
Hey, I'll owe you one.
我正在准备竞选市长
I am throwing my hat in for mayor.
Hale 没戏了
Hale's done.
到时我可能需要一些回报
I may need some favors.
有什么需要尽管说
Whatever you need.
保持联络
I'll be in touch.
嘿
Hey.
什么？
What?
宝贝 冷静
Babe, calm down.
多谢
Thanks.
不客气
No problem.
你有40分钟时间
You got 40 minutes.
我们知道规矩
We know the drill.
让“治疗”开始吧
Let the therapy begin.
布道结束了 白痴
Sermon's over, shithead.
嘿 老兄
Hey, man.
Jax要你去下厨房
Jax needs you in the kitchen.
什么事？
What's up?
地方检察官的最新消息
Update on the D.A.
你找Tara谈了
I talked to Tara.
妈的
Shit.
我告诉过你 我的家事你不能管
I told you my family is off-limits.
我只是想听听她的说法
I just wanted to hear her side.
这就是为什么你称她是骗子？
Is that why you called her a liar?
什么？
What?
我可没叫她...
I didn't call her no...
你说她是爱耍手腕的婊子
You said she was a manipulative bitch!
如果她是这样告诉你的 那么 我认为她就是的
If she told you that, well, then I guess she is.
好了 别这样
All right, come on.
这会儿 你不能进去 夫人
You don't want to go back there right now, ma'am.
听着 他们会为了我互相伤害
Look, they're gonna hurt each other 'cause of me.
行了 让开
Come on, break it up.
Hap 拜托了
Hap, please.
来吧
Let's go.
Jax  Jax 停手 别再打了
Jax, Jax, come on, break it up!
停手
Stop it!
停手 Jackson
Stop it, Jackson!
喔  喔   喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哦 老天
Oh, Jesus.
抱歉 老妈
I'm sorry, mama.
我不想...我不想发生这样的事情
I didn't want... I didn't want it to happen like this.
别抱歉
Don't be sorry.
她就是我们想干掉对方的根源
She's reason we're trying to kill each other.
老弟 你根本不知道她又为你做了什么
Man, you got no idea what she's done for you!
需要知道的我都很清楚 Nero
I know everything I need to know, Nero!
哦 是吗？
Oh, yeah?
你知道安排和Clay在监狱同房时发生了什么？
What about the little conjugal with Clay?
别说
Don't!
不 不 不 老妈
No, no, no, mama!
你告诉他
You told him what-what I did.
他必须知道...他必须明白你为他做了什么
Now he needs to know... he needs
to know what you've done for him.
那次和Clay发生什么事？
So what happened with Clay?
那几个监狱的看守
The guards from the cell.
强迫你老妈和Clay发生关系
They forced your mother to have sex with Clay.
他们在一边看着
While they watched.
他们还把裤子脱了
While they got off.
没关系的
It doesn't matter.
都过去了
It's done.
不 老妈
No, Mom.
我刚和Margaret谈过...她承认了你不愿意相信的事实
I just talked to Margaret... who
confirmed what you refuse to believe.
亲爱的 这一切都是谎言
Honey, it was all a lie.
不管是怀孕 还是流产
The pregnancy, the miscarriage.
Tara想离开 Jax
Tara wants out, Jax.
离开你 离开帮会 离开Charming镇
You, the club, Charming.
她在申请离婚 她会把你的孩子从你身边带走
She's filing for divorce, and she's
gonna take your boys away from you.
离开我们大家
From all of us.
还有 亲爱的 我很遗憾
And, honey, I'm sorry.
我也很喜欢她
I love her, too.
但这是事实
But this is the truth.
假如她没打算告诉你 你必须找一个愿意告诉你的人
And if she's not gonna tell you,
you need to find someone who will.
谢谢光临
Thanks for coming.
哈
Yeah.
听上去很重要
Sounded important.
确实是的
It is.
是关于Tara和孩子们的事
It's about Tara and the kids.
来 这边请
Here, come this way, please.
有请
Come on.
请坐
Just... have a seat.
我...马上就回来
I-I'll be right back.
坐下
Sit... down.
我不想被迫伤害你 Lowen
I don't want to have to hurt you, Lowen.
我要问你几个问题
I need to ask you some questions.
请别这样
Please don't do this.
Tara打算和我离婚吗？
Is Tara divorcing me?
回答我
Answer me!
是的
Yes.
还要带走我的孩子们
And taking my sons?
还有怀孕的事..
The pregnancy...
我不是....
I didn't...
到底是不是...是不是谎言
Was it...! Was it a lie?
是的 我想是的
Yes, I think so.
为什么？
Why?
为了监护权
Custody waiver.
这样Gemma就不能带走孩子们了
So Gemma couldn't take the boys.
求你别伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
滚出去
Get out.
Tara只是想...
Tara was just trying...
滚出去
Get out!
你得到你所需要的？
You get what you needed?
是啊
Yeah.
你向我保证过的 孩子
You made me a promise, son.
不可以有人受到伤害
Nobody gets hurt.
是的
Yeah.
没人会受到伤害
Nobody gets hurt.
喂
Hello.
Tara 我是Ally Lowen
Tara, it's Ally Lowen.
为什么你要去找Tara？
Why'd you go to Tara?
我可不喜欢那样
It's not what I wanted.
我也不知道
I don't know.
原以为 要是她知道了造成了这么严重的后果...
I thought maybe if she knew
all the damage that was being done...
我估计事与愿违吧
I guess that backfired.
是啊
Yeah.
她还说了你的事
She had some things to say about you.
我想肯定会的
I'm sure she did.
是关于John的
About John.
他告诉你什么？
What'd she tell you?
说是你杀了他
That you killed him.
真相时什么？
Any truth to that?
John当时希望帮会退出枪支生意
John was trying to get the club out of guns.
那时候局势和现在一样紧张
It was as tense then as it is now.
他来来回回去贝尔法斯特好几次
He was making trips back and forth to Belfast,
试图和爱尔兰人把这事情谈妥
trying to make it right with the Irish.
那时他爱上另一个人
He fell in love with someone.
就是Maureen Ashby
Maureen Ashby.
他哥哥是一位牧师 John的老朋友
Brother was a priest,friend of John's,
帮忙做中间人 使得能与爱尔兰共和军和平过渡
helping broker a peaceful transition with the IRA.
我新发现后
I found out.
开始和Clay混在了一起
Started spending time with Clay.
我的小儿子Thomas就是John不在家时死了
My Thomas died when John was away on one of those trips.
他回来以后 我也不再温柔娴淑
And I wasn't kind when he got home.
失去孩子的愤怒和痛苦 我要他也尝尝
The pain and anger of losing my
baby, I made sure it landed on him.
从那时起 他就能人事了
He came undone after that.
与IRA的谈判也谈崩了
Talks with the IRA fell apart.
Clay 和 McGee勾搭在一起 又开始做枪支生意
Clay and McGee put them back together again.
从另一个方面
In the other direction.
使得帮会更加深的陷入枪支生意
Solidified the gun trade for the club.
他们开始掌权
Made them players.
然而JT....他开始把这一切写进他的日记里 一部手稿
But JT... he started writing in this...
this journal, a manuscript.
那是赤裸裸的忏悔 怀疑他所有的选择
It was a bleeding confession,questioning all his choices,
对所有他为帮会做过的一切都感到懊悔
regretting everything he'd ever done in SAMCRO.
他不再关心帮会
He stopped caring about the club.
不关心家人
About his family.
那时候正是危机四伏的时刻
And it was a dangerous time here.
和玛雅帮的争斗
Mayan war.
联邦调查局的渗透
Feds infiltrating MCs.
人人自危
Everyone was scared.
JT是最薄弱的一环
JT was a weak link.
你没有回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question.
我没有杀他
I didn't kill him.
但是我知道 他肯定会被干掉
But I knew it had to be done.
就如同不得不处理Arcadio一样
The same way you knew it had to be done with Arcadio.
我们死也好活也好 都是这规矩
We live and die by that code.
现在我知道 那时候我也知道
I know it now, and I knew it then.
我不会对我深爱的男人有任何的隐瞒
And I did not hide my opinion from
the man I'd fallen in love with.
Clay 要杀 John Teller 我给了我的祝福
I gave my blessing for Clay to kill John Teller.
这事我没有告诉过任何人
I've never told that to anyone.
包括我的儿子
Including my son.
老天 Jackie
Jesus Christ, Jackie.
你没事吧？
You okay?
我很好
I'm all right.
你的那个小朋友来了
Your little girlfriend's here.
想谈谈
Wants to talk.
那个扳手女孩？
Girl with the wrench?
是的
Yeah.
她不肯说什么
She hasn't said much.
除非要见到你
Except that she needs to see you.
让我和她单独聊聊
Let me talk to her alone.
她又没被人包裹起来
She ain't packing.
走了
Go.
好了 都起来
All right, get up.
到楼上去
Upstairs.
还有你 笛子先生
You, too, Mr. Kazoo.
那个吹笛子的人很有趣
Guy with the kazoo's pretty interesting.
我们是在家门口的一个篮子里发现他的
We found him in a basket on our doorstep.
怎么回事？
What happened?
被水管扳手给打了
Got hit with a pipe wrench.
哦 我...我对窗子的事情抱歉...还有那车
Yeah, I'm... I'm sorry about the window...and the bike.
我和你老爸聊过了
I talked to your dad.
我知道
I know.
我...我也说不清怎么回事
I-I'm... I'm not really sure what happened.
我是说 我发现那篇报道 我知道你们
I mean, I-I found the article, and
I knew you guys moved in here.
我 我有点...脑子有点短路了
I-I've got some... some shit going
on, you know, in... in my head.
我知道
We all do.
我老爸...我老爸说你..你和他的老板谈过
My dad... my dad said you-you talked with his boss.
他会帮我们留下那所房子
He's gonna help us keep the house.
你为什么要这样做 即使我做了出格的事？
Why would you do that after what I did?
我是我向你老妈致歉意的方式
It's just my way of saying sorry to a mother.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祈愿你的美梦在暗夜中带给你安宁
May your dreams Bring you peace in the darkness
祈愿你在风雨中也能乐观积极 祈愿上天之光芒
May your head rise over The rain May the light from above
永远引导你去爱
Always lead you to love
祈愿你永远得到天使庇护
May you stay in the arms of the angels
祈愿你永远在阴影中无惧
May you always be brave In the shadows...
直到阳光重新照耀在你的身上
Till the sun shines upon you again
在我心底 听见这些祈愿
Hear this prayer In my heart
我们将永不分离
And we'll ne'er be apart
祈愿你永远得到天使庇护
May you stay in the arms of the angels
祈愿你听见林间的每首天籁之音
May you hear every song...In the forest
倘若你迷失了前行的道路
And if ever you lose your own way...
听听我的声音
Hear my voice
就像微风轻轻吹拂树梢...
Like a breeze Whisper soft through the trees...
祈愿你永远得到天使庇护
May you stay in the arms of the angels
祈愿你茁壮成长 成为顶天立地的 一个男子汉 ，我亲爱的
May you grow up to stand As a man, love...
以家族的名字为荣耀
With the pride of your family and name
当你躺到床上
When you lay down your head
好好休息时
For to rest in your bed
祈愿你永远得到天使庇护
May you stay in the arms of the angels
原创翻译 倾情奉献
英语字幕：n17t01   翻译：Wilsonyy  校对：Dena